vimo.com 2009-06-25

# Privacy Statement at Vimo - Comparison Shopping for Health Insurance

Vimo is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and security. We understand the nature of the information entrusted to us and make every effort to protect such information according our established security policies. 

These security policies and the technologies underlying them are reviewed on a regular basis as we continually evaluate new technologies to ensure that your data receives the best possible protection. 

**We do not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties at any time**. 

**Limited Exceptions**

**Your personal information is transmitted to our vendors or partners only under the following limited circumstances:**

  * Insurance Companies and Licensed Agents: Inquiries and applications for insurance products or requests for quotes may be transmitted to the insurance company that you have chosen, or to a licensed agent of the company for processing. These partners are obligated to maintain your confidentiality, and will only use your information for follow-up on your application, request for information or a quote. 
  * HSA Trustees and Third Party Administrators: If you express interest in a health savings account (HSA) or healthcare reimbursement account (HRA) vendor with whom we are affiliated, we may disclose information to that trustee or their administrator for follow-up and processing. These affiliates are obligated to maintain your confidentiality, and will only use your information for follow-up on your application or request for information. 
  * Legal or Regulatory: We may disclose your information to legal or law enforcement authorities to cooperate with inquiries from such organizations or if disclosure is required under the law. 

Please be assured that, outside of these exceptions, **your personal information will not be shared with any third parties.**

**Information we collect**

_Registration Information_

We collect some information about you and your company when you register with us. You can register with us through our website by providing your email address and choosing your password. This information is collected for communication with you and for identification and authorization the next time you return to the site. 

Company Information

In the course of your usage of the site, we may collect additional information about your company, the number of employees, average age of your employees, and so on. This information is collected in order to make recommendations and provide cost estimates for plans that may be of interest to you. 

_Benefit Preferences_

Our decision support tools enable you to compare and rank benefits based on your criteria, and store plan data that may be of interest. This data is stored so as to enable you to resume your work on subsequent visits, and to enable follow-up from us if requested. 

_Employee Information_

Personal information about your employees is required in the event you request a quote.Any such information is held in the strictest confidence, and will only be shared as specified above with the companies or agents that generate the quote. 

_Anonymous Information_

We collect anonymous information regarding site traffic and usage patterns for internal purposes, and may share it with third parties without any identifying information. This information is used primarily to improve our service and product offerings.“Cookies” are small browser data files that reside on your computer and enable us to recognize you if you return to our site at a later time using the same computer. 

_Security_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information provided online, Vimo has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. Vimo uses industry-recognized security Best Practices to help protect your business, financial, and personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access,disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**Changes to Policies**

Our privacy and security policies are reviewed from time to time. Any changes to policies will be posted to our website so users are always aware of how we use the information we collect. 

Your personally identifiable information collected to process your request might include your name, mailing address, telephone number, fax number and/or email address. Additionally, we collect information relating to the primary applicant and all the additional insureds: names, age, height/weight and other information necessary to provide a quote on insurance. All customer information we collect is strictly confidential. Our participating insurance professionals, to whom this information is referred, are bound by the same terms of confidentiality. Your information is used for rating purposes only for the insurance coverage(s) requested, and to contact you for the purposes of completing and providing you with the requested quotes. 

The contact information you submit through the online forms that appear on our websites is used to send you information about health insurance plans. You may also be contacted by insurance representatives directly. Some of these contacts may take the form of email sent to the email address you provide to us. You may also be contacted by telephone or via US mail if you provide that contact information to us. If you do not wish to be contacted by Vimo or its affiliated insurance representatives please click here to unsubscribe. Vimo will attempt to ensure that any such direct contact is made in accordance with all applicable state and federal laws and regulations, such as the Federal CAN-SPAM Act. 

Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Vimo will NOT provide any personally identifying information, regardless of source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. Aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information may be provided to reputable third-party vendors, but these figures will include no personally identifying information. 

**Children's Privacy**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Vimo.com and our affiliated websites are not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Cookies**

We make use of cookies for all websites visitors to collect aggregate information on the number of visitors to our site and other information about the number of pages viewed on the site. In certain circumstances, we may assign visitors completing online forms posted on this site a unique identifier cookie. Cookie information is used only by Vimo, Inc and organizations under contract to Vimo to analyze, track and optimize traffic on our websites. Cookie data is used in aggregate for traffic analysis, to provide relevant information to our visitors. It is also used in the aggregate for websites and system administration, including research and development, user analysis and business decision-making. Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use tracking technologies by or through the Site. We have no control over what information such third parties track or collect, and we have no responsibility or liability for any tracking, data collection or other activities of such third parties. 

**FOR WEBSITE VISITORS WHO DO NOT PROVIDE IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

If you do not provide information on the forms posted on our websites, our web server will not access or have access to your personally identifying information. We will not know your email address unless you volunteer it. You should know, however, that much of the most valuable information provided to visitors by Vimo is available only to visitors who complete forms on our websites. This is a website maintained on behalf of: Vimo, Inc. While Vimo takes all reasonable precautions, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.
